{
    "subject": "resource/Tom_Clancy's_Splinter_Cell",
    "predicate": "property/game",
    "object": "resource/Tom_Clancy's_Splinter_Cell:_Chaos_Theory",
    "human_readable": "Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell is a game.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9670148491859436,
            "question": "Is Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell a book or a game?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9425169229507446,
            "question": "Name some popular features of the 'Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell' series."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8648653030395508,
            "question": "What is the main theme of the game Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.693076491355896,
            "question": "What platform was the first 'Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell' game released on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6591963171958923,
            "question": "Who created the franchise 'Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6335117816925049,
            "question": "What kind of character is the protagonist in Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6141800880432129,
            "question": "What type of media is Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6097293496131897,
            "question": "Is there a movie based on Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5557088255882263,
            "question": "What genre does Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell likely belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45708775520324707,
            "question": "How many installments are there in the 'Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell' franchise?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell is a game.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5121_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre does Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell likely belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5121_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a movie based on Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5121_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of media is Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5121_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5121_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5121_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5121_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5121_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5121_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5121_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5121_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5121_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5121_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5121_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as it is explicitly stated that \"Tom Clancy\u2019s Splinter Cell is a popular stealth-action video game series developed by Ubisoft.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly describe \"Tom Clancy\u2019s Splinter Cell\" as a video game series, which supports the statement that it is a game."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}